Carl's giving me a hard time.
Carl's让我很难受.
Why?
为什么?
He says I should be in better shape.
他说我需要更好的身材.
What is he talking about? You look fine.
他在说些什么啊? 你看起来很好.
Carl says he works out three times a week.
Carl说他一个星期锻炼三次.
He goes to a gym.
他去健身房.
So what?
那又怎么样?
He says he does it for work.
他说他做这些是为了工作.
So he can lift the bags.
So 他能举起行李.
Well, that's fine for him.
Well, 他那样做是可以的.
That's not all.
那还不是全部.
He says he quit smoking.
他说他戒烟了.
Ah, except for the occasional cigarette he sneaks.
Ah, 除了偶尔他会偷偷抽几根.
He does? How do you know?
他有吗? 你怎么知道?
I sneak with him. Occasionally.
我跟他一起偷着抽. 偶尔.
He told me he eats healthy,
他告诉我他吃健康,
balanced meals.
营养均衡的食品.
What?
Carl"Make-That-A-Large-Pepperoni-Pizza"?
"把它弄成大号意大利辣香肠披萨"的Carl?
"Apple-Pie-and-Ice-Cream" Carl?
"苹果派加冰淇淋"的Carl?
Peter.
Carl never met a French fry he didn't like.
Carl从来没遇到过他不喜欢的炸薯条.
But he said...
但是他说...
Hi Carl!
What have you got there?
你那儿拿了些什么?
Hi. just a little lunch.
Hi.一点儿午餐而已.
Low fat yogurt. Tuna salad.
低脂酸奶. 金枪鱼沙拉.
Chocolate cake.
巧克力蛋糕.
Hey, a guy's got to eat.
Hey, 一个人总得吃东西呀!